Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1412
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, December 26, 1950; 25.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Per Capita, December 28, 1950; 26.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1952 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Julius Emspak to Sandra Martin Regarding Strikes, January 2, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, January 10, 1951; 2.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, January 25, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, February 2, 1951; 4.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Finances, March 8, 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Telephone List, November 26, 1951; 6.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Finances and Local 1008, February 19, 1952; 7.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, July 11, 1952; 8.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, October 9, 1952; 9.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, October 10, 1952; 10.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, October 17, 1952; 11.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, October 24, 1952; 12.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, October 31, 1952; 13.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, November 7, 1952; 14.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, November 14, 1952; 15.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, November 25, 1952; 16.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, December 3, 1952; 17.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, December 5, 1952; 18.
      - Chester Fisher to Martin Regarding Officers, January 27, 1947; 19.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Martin Regarding Officers, January 27, 1947; 20.
      - Fitzgerald to Martin Regarding Lea Case and Factionalism, April 8, 1948; 21.
      - Fitzgerald to Martin Regarding Tenth Anniversary, June 14, 1948; 22.
      - Fitzgerald to Martin Regarding Lea Case and Factionalism, January 14, 1949; 23.
      - Leo Jandreau to Martin Regarding White Collar Organization and GE Conference Board, November 22, 1943; 24.
      - Jandreau to Martin Regarding GE Organization, March 7, 1944; 25.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1952 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - James Matles to Martin Regarding Membership Activities, July 9, 1943; 1.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding White Collar Workers, August 14, 1946; 2.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Staff Members, December 30, 1946; 3.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Westinghouse Organization and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, March 4, 1947; 4.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Joshua Hardy Organization and USWA and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, March 4, 1947; 5.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Glenn Roberts Organization, March 5, 1947; 6.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Finances, November 19, 1947; 7.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Finances, December 16, 1947; 8.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding Staff Members, October 21, 1948; 9.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding GE Negotiations and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 9, 1951; 10.
      - Matles to Martin Regarding GE Oakland and Inter-union Rivalry, October 15, 1952; 11.
      - Edward Matthews to Martin Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, July 3, 1946; 12.
      - David Ratner to Martin Regarding Finances, February 11, 1949; 13.
      - Ben Riskin to Martin Regarding Westinghouse Contracts, June 6, 1946; 14.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding General Cable Unemployment, June 7, 1946; 15.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding Wages, July 11, 1946; 16.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding Negotiations and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, June 25, 1946; 17.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding Phelps Dodge Strike and General Cable Job Classifications, July 10, 1946; 18.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding General Cable Negotiations, October 3, 1946; 19.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding General Cable Negotiations, Grievances, and Factionalism, August 19, 1947; 20.
      - Riskin to Martin Regarding Rome General Cable Strike, October 10, 1950; 21.
      - Anthony Salese to Martin Regarding Bayonne General Cable and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 13, 1944; 22.
      - David Scribner to Martin Regarding Glenn Roberts Contract, October 8, 1945; 23.
      - Scribner to Martin Regarding Finances, June 30, 1952; 24.
      - Albert Smith to Martin Regarding Staff Members, August 19, 1946; 25.
      - Joseph Turkowski to Martin Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 26.
      - A. Yatsko to Martin Regarding General Cable, January 31, 1944; 27.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Sandra Martin to Julius Emspak Regarding Contracts, February 20, 1943; 1.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Contracts, April 29, 1943; 2.
      - Martin to Gardner Electric Regarding Negotiations, June 28, 1943; 3.
      - Martin to W.B. Griswold Regarding General Cable Negotiation, June 28, 1943; 4.
      - Martin to James Matles Regarding Negotiations and General Cable, August 4, 1943; 5.
      - Martin to Ed Matthews Regarding Grievances and Westinghouse, August 16, 1943; 6.
      - Martin to Omar Hoskins Regarding General Cable Negotiation, September 1, 1943; 7.
      - Martin to A. Yatso Regarding Officers and GE Productivity, November 9, 1943; 8.
      - Martin to J. Hood Regarding GE Grievances, November 10, 1943; 9.
      - Martin to Leo Jandreau Regarding Women and GE, November 17, 1943; 10.
      - Martin to Jandreau Regarding Officers and Oakland General Cable Organization, February 15, 1944; 11.
      - Martin to Carl Brant Regarding General Cable White Collar Organization, June 8, 1944; 12.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Local 420 and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 17, 1944; 13.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, August 3, 1944; 14.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding General Cable Office Organization, December 15, 1944; 15.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding General Cable Office Organization, January 4, 1945; 16.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, March 29, 1945; 17.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Policy Conference, July 21, 1945; 18.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Glenn Roberts Negotiation, September 29, 1945; 19.
      - Martin to David Scribner Regarding Glenn Roberts Negotiation, September 29, 1945; 20.
      - Martin to James Matles Regarding Strike, Western Electric, and National Federation of Telephone Workers, September 29, 1945; 21.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Leaving Local 1412, January 13, 1946; 22.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Outgoing Correspondence, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Sandra Martin to Julius Emspak Regarding Heintz & Kaufman Strike and International Association of Machinists, February 1, 1946; 1.
      - Martin to UE Regarding Radio Broadcasts, February 15, 1946; 2.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Exide Strike, March 25, 1946; 3.
      - Martin to Ed Matthews Regarding White Collar Workers and Strikes, April 2, 1946; 4.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Strikes, April 30, 1946; 5.
      - Martin to Ben Riskin Regarding General Cable Conference, May 2, 1946; 6.
      - Martin to General Cable Contract, May 24, 1946; 7.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding General Cable Contract, May 27, 1946; 8.
      - Martin to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, June 4, 1946; 9.
      - Martin to Chester Fisher Regarding Contracts and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, June 4, 1946; 10.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding IBEW and General Cable Unemployment, June 4, 1946; 11.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding American Meter Negotiations with Pay Rates, June 4, 1946; 12.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry and Los Angeles General Cable Unemployment, June 15, 1946; 13.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding General Cable White Collar Negotiations, July 10, 1946; 14.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Finances and Strikes, June 5, 1946; 15.
      - Martin to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Seattle Negotiations, June 24, 1946; 16.
      - Martin to Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Seattle and American Federation of Labor Negotiations, June 26, 1946; 17.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding American Meter Negotiations with Wage Rates, July 3, 1946; 18.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding Phelps Dodge Strike, July 3, 1946; 19.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding General Cable Strike, Unemployment, and Officers, July 3, 1946; 20.
      - Martin to Riskin Regarding Phelps Dodge Strike, July 5, 1946; 21.
      - Martin to James Matles Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, July 31, 1946; 22.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Outgoing Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Sandra Martin to James Matles Regarding Glenn Roberts Runaway Shops, October 16, 1946; 1.
      - Martin to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, October 30, 1946; 2.
      - Martin to Albert Smith Regarding Westinghouse Seattle Negotiations and Organization, November 8, 1946; 3.
      - Martin to UE Regarding PAC, December 26, 1946; 4.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 27, 1946; 5.
      - Martin to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, January 20, 1947; 6.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 30, 1947; 7.
      - Martin to Edward Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Emeryville and Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions Inter-union Rivalry, February 14, 1947; 8.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Glenn Roberts Indianapolis Organization with March 5, 1947, Matles Letter to Robert Kirkwood, February 15, 1947; 9.
      - Martin to Phillip Murray Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, Factionalism, and Civil Rights, February 15, 1947; 10.
      - Martin to Harry Truman Regarding Civil Rights, February 15, 1947; 11.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Joshua Hendy and United Steelworkers and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, February 26, 1947; 12.
      - Martin to David Scribner Regarding Westinghouse Emeryville Office Workers, Inter-union Rivalry, and National Labor Relations Board, March 11, 1947; 13.
      - Martin to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse Emeryville and Bowman Firing, March 28, 1947; 14.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Factionalism, March 30, 1947; 15.
      - Martin to Joseph Dermody Regarding GE and Union Membership, April 14, 1947; 16.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding GE and Membership, April 14, 1947; 17.
      - Martin to Matthews Regarding Westinghouse and Membership, April 14, 1947; 18.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Sandra Martin to Julius Emspak Regarding Exide Negotiations, May 21, 1947; 1.
      - Martin to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, Taft-Hartley, and General Strike, June 23, 1947; 2.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Grievances, Factionalism, and Unemployment, August 9, 1947; 3.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Grievances, General Cable, and Unemployment, August 14, 1947; 4.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Publicity, September 2, 1947; 5.
      - Martin to Bill Elconin Regarding Staff Members, September 13, 1947; 6.
      - Martin to Russ Nixon Regarding PAC, September 13, 1947; 7.
      - Martin to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Finances, December 29, 1947; 8.
      - Martin to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Lea Case, May 11, 1948; 9.
      - Martin to Nixon Regardig PAC, May 19, 1948; 10.
      - Martin to Fitzgerald Regarding Tenth Anniversary, June 8, 1948; 11.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 3, 1948; 12.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding Local 107 and Red-baiting, August 21, 1948; 13.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding CIO Convention, September 13, 1948; 14.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding California Visit, October 1, 1948; 15.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 16, 1948; 16.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding GE San Jose, November 16, 1948; 17.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding General Cable Negotiation, November 29, 1948; 18.
      - Martin to David Ratner Regarding Finances, February 2, 1949; 19.
      - Martin to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Lea Case, April 12, 1944; 20.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, December 28, 1950; 21.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, January 4, 1951; 22.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, January 16, 1951; 23.
      - Martin to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, January 31, 1951; 24.
      - Martin to Joseph Dermody Regarding GE Strike, March 16, 1951; 25.
      - Martin to Matles Regarding General Executive Board, September 8, 1952; 26.
    - Local 1412 General Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1955 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - James Carey to W.E. Murphy Regarding Local 1222 Strike, December 19, 1938; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Murphy Regarding Strike Fund, July 28, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mergenthaler Strike, December 28, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Velma Prindle Regarding Strike Fund, February 15, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to W. Murphy Regarding Ford Boycott, February 27, 1939; 5.
      - Emspak to Prindle Regarding Per Capita, July 5, 1939; 6.
      - Emspak to A.R. Moneton Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, September 14, 1939; 7.
      - Emspak to William Stevenson Regarding Per Capita, April 4, 1940; 8.
      - Emspak to Kenneth Durden Regarding Honorary Membership, February 20, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Durden Regarding Local 747, August 4, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak to Durden Regarding Constitutions, April 8, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Elaine Yoneda Regarding Dues and Veterans, March 20, 1945; 12.
      - Emspak to Vernon Sweet Regarding Finances and Arbitration, July 17, 1953; 13.
      - Emspak to Sweet Regarding Finances, Arbitration, and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 29, 1954; 14.
      - Emspak to Sweet Regarding Finances, March 3, 1955; 15.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Elconin Regarding Pacific Coast Conference, June 17, 1955; 16.
      - Leslie Lubliner to UE Regarding Westinghouse Emeryville White Collar Workers and Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions Inter-union Rivalry, March 4, 1947; 17.
      - James Matles to W. Mitchell Regarding Westinghouse Organization, March 4, 1938; 18.
      - Matles to W. Murphy Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, November 11, 1938; 19.
      - Matles to Mitchell Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, December 5, 1938; 20.
      - Matles to Mitchell Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, January 31, 1939; 21.
      - Matles to Mitchell Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, February 15, 1939; 22.
      - Matles to Mitchell Regarding Staff Members, April 24, 1939; 23.
    - Local 1412 General Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - James Matles to W. Murphy Regarding Westinghouse Organization, June 21, 1939; 1.
      - Matles to Murphy Regarding GE Contract and Grievances, September 25, 1939; 2.
      - Matles to Bob Dealey Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation, March 27, 1941; 3.
      - Matles to Dealey Regarding Bargaining Unit, April 26, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Robert Burke Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation, February 13, 1942; 5.
      - Matles to William Stevenson Regarding Strikes, March 8, 1946; 6.
      - Matles to Local 1412 Regarding Staff Members, July 8, 1946; 7.
      - Matles to Vernon Sweet Regarding Finances and Grievances, July 30, 1953; 8.
      - Albert Olson to J. Kennety Durden Regarding Bonding, March 27, 1942; 9.
      - Joseph Pleszeski to Norman Jacobs Regarding GE Negotiation and Local 618, June 8, 1942; 10.
      - Ben Riskin to Stevenson Regarding Phelps Dodge Strike, July 8, 1946; 11.
      - Riskin to Local 1412 Regarding General Cable Negotiation, March 28, 1949; 12.
      - J.B. Steckley to Murphy Regarding General Cable, April 25, 1939; 13.
    - Local 1412 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Clinton Apedaile to UE Regarding Officers, October 1939; 1.
      - Apedaile to Paul Schliff Regarding Organization, Political Action, Almeda County Congress of Industrial Organizations, and Factionalism, December 5, 1939; 2.
      - Isabel Berrisford to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 20, 1950; 3.
      - G. Brubaker to James Matles Regarding Unemployment and Negotiations, March 11, 1938; 4.
      - Robert Burke to Matles Regarding Negotiations, January 16, 1942; 5.
      - George Daskalos to Emspak Regarding GE Strike, February 10, 1951; 6.
      - J. Durden to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 26, 1940; 7.
      - Durden to Emspak Regarding Local 747, August 1, 1941; 8.
      - Durden to Emspak Regarding Officers, February 1, 1942; 9.
      - Duke Fregi to Emspak Regarding Local 132 Strike, April 27, 1940; 10.
      - Fregi to Matles Regarding Gardner Contract, July 20, 1940; 11.
      - Martha Hans to Ben Riskin Regarding Westinghouse Contract, May 21, 1946; 12.
      - Walter Hutzler to Phillip Murray Regarding CIO and Factionalism, May 10, 1948; 13.
      - Robert Keys to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation, December 6, 1940; 14.
      - Walter Lea to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, March 30, 1948; 15.
      - Lea to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, January 10, 1949; 16.
      - A. Moreton to Emspak Regarding CIO Convention, September 18, 1939; 17.
      - W.E. Murphy to William Mitchell Regarding General Cable Negotiation, July 1, 1938; 18.
      - Murphy to James Carey Regarding Staff Members, October 1, 1938; 19.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Unemployment and UE News, October 15, 1938; 20.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Local 1222 Strike, December 12, 1938; 21.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Local 1222 Strike, December 16, 1938; 22.
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 31, 1939; 23.
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Ford Boycott, February 20, 1939; 24.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Wages, March 20, 1939; 25.
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Political Action, April 5, 1939; 26.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding General Cable and Negotiations, April 17, 1939; 27.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 17, 1939; 28.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Local 1002 Boycott, April 21, 1939; 29.
      - Murphy to J.B. Steckley Regarding General Cable, May 1, 1939; 30.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Unemployment, July 2, 1939; 31.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Allen-Bradley Strike with July 24, 1939, Murphy Letters to Allen-Bradley and Robert Dealey, 32.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation, August 21, 1939; 33.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Grievances, September 18, 1939; 34.
      - Murphy to Carey Regarding Staff Members, September 18, 1939; 35.
    - Local 1412 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1955 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Velma Pridle to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 30, 1938; 1.
      - Bob Ringel to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, June 11, 1946; 2.
      - Ringel to Ben Regarding Contracts and Seniority, July 26, 1936; 3.
      - William Stevenson to Emspak Regarding Dues, July 23, 1938; 4.
      - Stevenson to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members, February 12, 1945; 5.
      - Stevenson to Emspak Regarding GM Negotiations, May 25, 1938; 6.
      - Vernon Sweet to Emspak Regarding Strikes, July 15, 1952; 7.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding General Cable Strike, October 15, 1952; 8.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding General Cable Strike, October 30, 1952; 9.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding General Cable Strike, November 24, 1952; 10.
      - Sweet to James Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 20, 1953; 11.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Grievances, Arbitration, and Inter-union Rivalry, July 6, 1953; 12.
      - Sweet to Joseph Dermody Regarding Finances and Grievances, July 13, 1953; 13.
      - Sweet to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances, November 13, 1953; 14.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Finances and Arbitration, March 26, 1954; 15.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Finances and Arbitration, April 20, 1954; 16.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 24, 1955; 17.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 9, 1955; 18.
      - Sweet to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 11, 1955; 19.
      - Gertrude Wilson to Fitzgerald Regarding Wages, February 2, 1951; 20.
      - Elaine Yoneda to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, March 5, 1945; 21.
      - Local 1412 to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, June 6, 1946; 22.
      - Local 1412 Officers to Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action, March 30, 1948; 23.
      - Local 1412 Westinghouse Shop Committee to J.W. Ryan Regarding Negotiation, January 21, 1939; 24.
    - Local 1412 Notices of Delinquency, November 1937-March 1938 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Local 1412 Reports of Financial Secretary, June-August 1937 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Local 1412 Per Capita Reports, September 1937-June 1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Local 1412 Per Capita Reports, July 1939-July 1940 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Local 1412 Finances, 1937-1955 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Per Capita Payments, 1937-1939; 1.
      - General Cable Office Organizing Expenses, January 1945; 2.
      - John Kraft Seattle Expenses, September 18, 1946; 3.
      - Lost Time, October 10, 1955; 4.
    - Local 1412 Financial Reports, July-November 1947 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Local 1412 Publications, 1939-1950, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Industrial Relations Policies Regarding General Cable, September 1939; 1.
      - UE 1412 Currents Newspaper, January 20, 1950; 2.
      - Newspaper Clipping Regarding GE Strike, n.d.; 3.
      - "You Can Do It Too" Leaflet Regarding Organization and Gardner Electric Contract, 4.
    - Local 1412 Emeryville Westinghouse Organization, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Leo Turner to James Matles, October 21, 1938; 1.
      - Turner to Matles, November 11, 1938; 2.
      - Letter to J.W. Ryan, November 11, 1938; 3.
      - Turner to Matles, January 21, 1939; 4.
      - Turner to Ryan, January 30, 1939; 5.
      - Turner to Matles, February 3, 1939; 6.
      - Turner to Matles, March 8, 1939; 7.
      - Julius Emspak to Turner, May 25, 1939; 8.
    - Local 1412 General Cable Negotiations, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - James Matles to Moss Kent, June 26, 1940; 1.
      - Kent to Matles, June 27, 1940; 2.
      - Kent to Matles with Proposed Contracts, July 2, 1940; 3.
      - Matles to Kent, August 21, 1940; 4.
      - Kent to Matles, August 29, 1940; 5.
    - Local 1412 Constitution, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, November 24, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Turner, December 15, 1941; 2.
    - Local 1412 Westinghouse Contracts, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Carl Brant to James Matles, June 17, 1942; 1.
      - Brant to Matles, July 30, 1942; 2.
      - Leo Turner to Matles, July 30, 1942; 3.
    - Local 1412 General Cable Overtime, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Carl Brant to Rodman with Brief, December 10, 1942; 1.
      - Brant to James Matles, December 11, 1942; 2.
      - Matles to Brant, January 20, 1942; 3.
    - Local 1412 Westinghouse Wages, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Leo Turner to James Matles, January 13, 1943; 1.
      - Matles to Turner, January 14, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1412 Headquarters, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak, April 29, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Brant, May 5, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Russ Nixon, May 5, 1943; 3.
    - Local 1412 General Cable Negotiations, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Carl Brant to James Matles, August 7, 1943; 1.